I sell luxury real estate, last year I did a million three, this year I'm on track to
do a million five.
Oh, sweet.
I would like to get to about 10 million.
What's stopping me is focus, apparently.
Right now, I started a fund and I want to be a developer as my end game.
And I also started doing paid ads.
I started doing paid ads in my real estate business and then I started paid ads for-
As an agency for others.
Yeah.
Of course, naturally.
Why wouldn't you?
You don't want to leave money on the table.
Yeah.
You're a realtor, right?
So you've got this business and then we've got agency, fund, and then your goal is to
be a developer over here.
They're all in real estate, though.
Yeah.
All of my businesses are- are businesses, isn't that like, same, same?
I hear you.
I'm just trying to make myself feel better.
So you want to do fund into development, right?
That's what you want to do.
Correct.
You could just do that.
How so?
You make a million plus a year, right?
You could stop doing that and then hit your base up and say, give me money, I'm going
to go develop properties now.
So why don't you do that?
Golden handcuffs, I guess.
Lifestyle?
Yeah.
I mean, it's just, how bad do you want it?
Do you want it enough that you would live in a different neighborhood, drive a different
car?
I'm married.
She's got to get it.
Dude, I get it.
I get it.
Honestly, it's a conversation.
Yeah.
It's like, sweetie, I know you love all this stuff, what if we had 10 times more stuff
than like five years?
I can take your number.
Yeah.